Micael Silva



micaelsilva.work@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mykaa



+351 968139550



https://mmykaa.github.io/

Summary

I started my journey in game programming when I was 14 to occupy my free time.

Nowadays I am a Gameplay Programmer with strong skills in C# and C++.

I am an expert user of Unity & Unreal Engine and have developed both personal and team projects within the engines.

Experience



Network / Gameplay Programmer @ Zapowa Games

Zapowa Games

Nov 2021 - Present (10 months +)

Unreal Engine / C++ / Gameplay / Networking / UI Programming

- Host / Join & Server Lists
- Arena Generation



UI / Gameplay Programmer @ WestFell Studios

WestFell Studios

Feb 2021 - Sep 2021 (8 months)

Unity / C# / Gameplay / Tools / UI Programming

- Console

Education



Polytechnic of Leiria

Undergraduate, Games and Multimedia Oct 2020 - Aug 2023

Licenses & Certifications



G Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design - Google

GRRV23TQ2BYA

Skills

Unreal Engine • C++ • Unity • C# • User Experience (UX)